Taejun doesn’t understand why that child is crying
He thought if there was a machine that could see through people's hearts
How nice it would be
Taejun
Where did he go?
But how could there be such a thing in the world?
Taejun
Amen
scalpel
Even if you open your body and cut open the flesh
Observe deeply
Taejun can never see through people's hearts
During that time he felt desperate
I feel like I am the only person in the world who is like this
But…
I don’t know if it’s luck or misfortune
his daughter was born
what she did
It's exactly the same as him
at that moment
He finally determined one thing
God will never make the same mistake over and over again
This means…
They are the chosen ones
["Good-natured Competition"]
Jay
great
How long do you want...
Go to the lockers at Exit 4
Let's get out of here first
So is this all a trap set by Jaro?
It's the man who came to school to find you before.
Do I want you to place an order?
Who is that person?
The person who gave me medicine for the first time
What a bastard
But it's also thanks to him
My grades can improve
Everyone's attitude towards me has also changed
Speaking of which, I should thank him
The phone you dialed is not turned on
Will be forwarded to voicemail
[Liu Jiena]
Liu Jiena should have been here...
The medicine was also taken away
Will she really be arrested by the police?
this is my purpose
what
Is it possible she could be going somewhere?
Like her favorite place
Or the home of a close friend of hers
Don't know
I don't know her very well
Don't you know her favorite singer...
Is it Lucid Fall?
Also
Don't worry too much
She shouldn't die anyway
who knows what will happen
You try calling her again
[Liu Jiena]
[Jena’s location]
Hey
Isn't this near your home?
Yes
In recent years, teenage patients who have come to me
Significantly more
Because I sit and read for a long time
Cause indigestion, constipation, gastroesophageal reflux
Various gastrointestinal diseases emerge in endlessly
I heard you also have two at home
Daughter preparing for exam
As a father of two daughters
Also a doctor…
Jay
No umbrella on a rainy day
You should call dad
The mock exam is coming soon. What should I do if I catch a cold?
Fortunately, no fever
But just in case
You'd better take a hot shower
Let's go to the hospital tomorrow and get an intravenous drip.
good
Dad
good night
good
You should also go to bed early
Teacher Yu’s mobile phone…
Gone
[Missed Call Little Bastard]
[Drug Abuse and Drug Prevention Promotional Video]
I had a headache but took digestive medicine
Indigestion
-Damn it
-Did you take headache medicine?
Does the school want us to go to college?
So annoying
That's right
Can't we touch the locker that's number one in the school?
why not check
Hello
Shut up and go to sleep
["Daejundong Valet Delivery Service"
A new post has been uploaded]
Nali
Your uniform will get dirty if you do this.
[Did Na Li transfer to another school because she was beaten by Jai?]
Jay
This is Jai's voice, right?
Oh my god, it's so scary
[Parents’ property and power = grades]
[Is the secret to getting number one in school a result of taking drugs?]
[The teachers didn’t dare to touch her either.
Her dad is the president of the parent association, and she is also number one in the school]
[No wonder her grades are so good. It turns out she relies on taking medicine]
Please watch this video carefully
Yesterday we received a
Report of drug dealing at Gangnam Station
This is the monitor picture of the locker being used at that time
If…
Does anyone know the identity of the man in the video?
or have heard of or witnessed any illegal drug dealing
Please provide clues to the police
Of course…
We will keep your identity confidential
Teacher Li, what's going on?
Principal
The detectives are coming...
You go back to the classroom to study immediately
Students, please stay where you are.
Go back quickly
We have spoken to students individually
You guys came to school suddenly like this?
That's too much
They are senior students in high school
Report call received last night
I took the call in the teacher's office at your school.
did you know
I know…
who is that person
Jay
The person caught on the surveillance camera
It's Liu Jiena
The daughter of the director of J Medical Center
Are you saying that the dean's daughter sells drugs?
how do you know
Because she is my sister
I've seen her steal medicine in the hospital many times
She should have been stopped then
Fanxiu may also be in school
Bought medicine from my sister
She was also at school on the school anniversary day
Then why did Fanxiu say that she bought it from Seulgi?
Because…
Seulgi is number one in the school
Everyone hates being number one in the school
madman
Did Beom Soo tell nonsense?
what are you talking about
Zhu Yili
So where is your sister now?
I don't know either
Since failing the college exam
I haven't seen her since
Please find her, officer.
Jay, wait for me
why do that
you don't have to be that way
Instead of letting my dad find my sister
It's better to let the police find it first
Were you really there on the school anniversary?
Have you met your sister?
We need to act quickly
what to do
Find evidence that Liu Jiena appeared
Dean Liu Taijun
I'm from the Female Juvenile Section of Gangnam Police Station.
Police officer Park Min-gyu
What's the matter?
Your daughter Jiena Liu is suspected of illegal drug dealing
we are looking for her
Please cooperate with the investigation
What are you doing?
How is it
You dress so much like a criminal, it scares me
They've all been searched, and there's nothing I can do about it.
Our fan show...
So pitiful
Quickly give me that you promised to give me
Hey, the victim personally wrote the petition for you.
You, the perpetrator, are still so arrogant?
It was you who first said you wanted to write it for me.
Wait
Answer me a question first
You said buying medicine from Seulgi was a lie, right?
Whose idea was it?
Do you want me to take a guess?
Found it
Wait
That's Xiao Jing, right?
what did they say
Why is Liu Jiena and Xiaojing together?
She should be finishing class soon
Do you know Xiaojing’s itinerary so well?
People come out
Hello Xiaojing
where are you
I'm having dinner with my mother
Let’s talk later
what did she say
She doesn't seem to be going to tutoring today
what
Oh
It seems she lied to us
You can just take the No. 300 bus back at the door.
That's not the direction to her home
Let’s go home each today
what
it's too late
Xiaojing may be busy with other things
ok
Xiaojing, why are you at my door?
what
Is this your home?
I don't know
Then what are you doing here?
You know what can be done
Borrowed
I do it every year
[Karma]
[There is no secret in the world]
[Why do you think your husband died]
What do you want to say
You should have heard about it just now
Sister Jenna is missing
What are you doing?
Did you already know this?
We see on the monitor
On the day of the school anniversary, you were with Sister Jina
If you knew that Liu Jiena was missing
should have told me earlier
Do I have an obligation to report everything to you?
Let’s talk about that day…
You used Seulgi as an excuse to run away.
We were all stuck in school
Hello
Jay, calm down
Xiaojing
can you tell us about that day
did you say anything to her
Sister Jina
Sister, what happened?
why are you here
Are you here to see Jay?
no...no
Then what are you doing here?
Do you know Yu Seqi?
You look for Seulgi...
what to do
do you know where she is
Sister, do you know whose daughter Yu Seqi is?
I just see your sister's style has changed
feel surprised
I just said hello to her first
Do you think I will believe it?
You have remained silent until now
It was your sister who told me not to tell you
I've seen her
Why did my sister do that?
Why are you suddenly worried about your sister?
Haven't your relationship always been bad?
Xiaojing…
I have known Liu Jieyi for six years
I've never heard of it in so long
she mentioned her sister
Now he is accused of being a drug dealer.
I just want to drag my sister out to take the blame.
If I were Sister Jina
I will definitely sever ties with you
you only care about yourself
I don’t care about the feelings of the people around me at all…
Still in the mood
Hello Yu Seqi
We are all just green leaves to set off her
[unknown number]
Who?
Hello
Yes, I am Liu Jieyi
Okay, tell me
Are you looking for your sister?
I know where Liu Jiena is now
who are you
It doesn't matter who I am
What you should ask is whether your sister is safe now
[unknown number]
[588-4 Gangnam-daero, Gangnam-gu, Seoul
H nightclub]
Bring 30 Kangsutin pills here before 1 o'clock
I'll tell you where Liu Jiena is
Jay
Really
You guys are leaving
How can I let you go alone?
too dangerous
That person is calling. Does that mean he knows something?
Let's go together then
No
He said he wanted me to go by myself
too dangerous
Let's go together
And your sister is missing
I also have a responsibility
Are you planning to...
Do you wear this to a nightclub?
Your clothes are a bit too big for me
Are there any smaller pieces?
Hello
Have you never put on makeup?
Open your eyes like this
Look down
Don’t act like you’re going to a nightclub for the first time
Hello Cui Jing
Wait
look down
Hey, you look like a high school student, right?
I'm not
what is not
Brother, take a look
It's because of the glasses
Isn't it a little strange?
The caller is a man
Why do you put things in the women's toilet?
He may have an accomplice
It's possible they took the money and ran away
Must catch people
I want a bottle of beer
bottle opener
Just turn away
Target appears
Target tracking
Girls’ toilets need support
give me a beer
Are you coming alone?
how old are you
Lost him. He may have gone to the second floor.
What clothes is that person wearing?
Wearing a T-shirt and a hat
Found someone
Jay